Guide to the National Law Center records, 1865-2005 RG0014
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Law alumni photographs, 1921-1989; RG0014 Series 13; 7.5 Linear feet (Box 9, Box 8, Box 7, Box 6, Box 13, Box 12, Box 11, Box 10, Box 15, Box 14, Box 1, Box 2, Box 3, Box 4, Box 5)
  - Correspondence between Lawerence McGril and Clifford Doughtery, 10/10/1975 --10/15/1975 (Box 12, Folder 211.2)
  - The Law Alumni News, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 211.3)
    Summer edition
  - Correspondence between C. Doughtery and V. Freeman, 08/28/1975 (Box 12, Folder 211.4)
    Contains a copy of the last issue of Law Alumni News
  - The Law Alumni News, undated (Box 12, Folder 211.5)
    Excerpt from newsletter
  - The Law Alumni News, undated (Box 12, Folder 211.6)
  - Curriculum Vitae- M. Cherif Bassiouni, undated (Box 12, Folder 211.7)
  - Photo of Clerance Wood and William M. Hobby, undated (Box 12, Folder 211.8)
  - Photo of Bob Rose, Judge Mildred, Reeves Sherman, Vance V. Vaughn, undated (Box 12, Folder 211.9)
  - Photo of 3 men and a women at a podium, undated (Box 12, Folder 211.1)
  - Photo of 3 men and a woman, undated (Box 12, Folder 211.11)
  - Newsletter for Feb. 1981, 02/1981 (Box 12, Folder 212.1)
    Law Alumni Newsletter
  - Newsletter for Feb. 1981, 02/1981 (Box 12, Folder 212.2)
    Report on the meeting of the GWLA meeting
  - Newsletter for Feb. 1981, 02/1981 (Box 12, Folder 212.3)
    President of LAA- address
  - Newsletter for Feb. 1981, 02/1981 (Box 12, Folder 212.4)
    Letter describing the 115th Annual Founders Day
  - Newsletter for Feb. 1981, 02/1981 (Box 12, Folder 212.5)
    Brief biography J. Dennis Malone
  - Newsletter for Feb. 1981, 02/1981 (Box 12, Folder 212.6)
    New Brief for Feb. 1981
  - Newsletter for Feb. 1981, 02/1981 (Box 12, Folder 212.7)
    Obituaries
  - Newsletter for Feb. 1981, 02/1981 (Box 12, Folder 212.8)
    Items for the LAA Newsletter
  - Newsletter for Feb. 1981, 02/1981 (Box 12, Folder 212.9)
    Dr. Robitscher speaks to Georgia Alumni
  - Newsletter for Feb. 1981, 02/1981 (Box 12, Folder 212.1)
    Helmuth's guide to source of financing and Walter
  - Newsletter for Feb. 1981, 02/1981 (Box 12, Folder 212.11)
    C. Dogherty's letter to Micheal D. Barnes
  - Newsletter for Feb. 1981, 02/1981 (Box 12, Folder 212.12)
    Calendar of GWLA Events
  - Newsletter for Feb. 1981, 02/1981 (Box 12, Folder 212.13)
    Description of the GWLA's next meeting
  - Newsletter for Feb. 1981, 02/1981 (Box 12, Folder 212.14)
    News items for the GWLA Newsletter
  - Newsletter for Feb. 1981, 02/1981 (Box 12, Folder 212.15)
    Calendar of Events of the GWLA
  - Newsletter for Feb. 1981, 02/1981 (Box 12, Folder 212.16)
    Fryer Portrait presented
  - Unused photos and articles for Feb. 1981, 02/1981 (Box 12, Folder 213.1)
    Article which describes the career and retirement of Lyle T. Alverson
  - Unused photos and articles for Feb. 1981, 02/1981 (Box 12, Folder 213.2)
    Whitcomb, Myra Barra, Lucero, Barra, Judge Campbel
  - Unused photos and articles for Feb. 1981, 02/1981 (Box 12, Folder 213.3)
    Howard P. Hoffman, Mermelstein, Dr. Jacob Burns, Robert Krammer,
  - Unused photos and articles for Feb. 1981, 02/1981 (Box 12, Folder 213.4)
    M. Byran Fisher and Dean Barron
  - Unused photos and articles for Feb. 1981, 02/1981 (Box 12, Folder 213.5)
    Marshall C. Gardener and his wife with William P. Smith
  - Unused photos and articles for Feb. 1981, 02/1981 (Box 12, Folder 213.6)
    Ann Fryer, William Fryer, Mary Frey, Mary Lee Fryer, Glen E. Weston, Prof. Chesterfield Oppenheim
  - Unused photos and articles for Feb. 1981, 02/1981 (Box 12, Folder 213.7)
    Betty Fryer, William T. Fryer
  - Unused photos and articles for Feb. 1981, 02/1981 (Box 12, Folder 213.8)
    Judy Dobbins, Dean Jerome Barrans and Allen T. Eaton
  - Unused photos and articles for Feb. 1981, 02/1981 (Box 12, Folder 213.9)
    Series of news items for the LAA newsletter
  - Unused photos and articles for Feb. 1981, 02/1981 (Box 12, Folder 213.1)
    Article on the National Conference on Women
  - Unused photos and articles for Feb. 1981, 02/1981 (Box 12, Folder 213.11)
    Article on the Annual Colorado Bar Breakfast
  - Unused photos and articles for Feb. 1981, 02/1981 (Box 12, Folder 213.12)
    Series of the News Briefs from the LAA newsletter
  - Newsletter, July 1977, undated (Box 12, Folder 214)
    Original photos in the GWU LAA photo collection
  - Pictures for Oct. 1976 Newsletter, 10/1976 (Box 12, Folder 215.1)
    Copies of orginial photos in the LAA
  - Pictures for Oct. 1976 Newsletter, 10/1976 (Box 12, Folder 215.2)
    John C. McNott, Elliot, LEster M. Ponder, Richard D. Gilroy, and Louis D. Nott[]per
  - Pictures for Oct. 1976 Newsletter, 10/1976 (Box 12, Folder 215.3)
  - Pictures for Oct. 1976 Newsletter, 10/1976 (Box 12, Folder 215.4)
    Copy of a photo of Judge Lawerence S. Margoli
  - Pictures for Oct. 1976 Newsletter, 10/1976 (Box 12, Folder 215.5)
    Invitation to the 1976 GWULAA Break
  - Newsletter, March 1986, 03/1986 (Box 12, Folder 216.1)
    Packet of articles from the GWULAA newsletter
  - Newsletter, March 1986, 03/1986 (Box 12, Folder 216.2)
    Announcement of the death of Glen A. Wilkinson
  - Newsletter, March 1986, 09/09/1985 (Box 12, Folder 216.3)
    Copy of the GW Report newsletter
  - Newsletter, March 1986, 08/09/1985 (Box 12, Folder 216.4)
    Resume of Marlana Valdez and letter from Dean Barron conerning Valdez's acceptance of the postion of Assis. Dean
  - Newsletter, March 1986, 03/1986 (Box 12, Folder 216.5)
    Items for the March LAA newsletter
  - Newsletter, March 1986, 03/1986 (Box 12, Folder 216.6)
    President's message for the LAA newsletter
  - Newsletter, March 1986, 03/1986 (Box 12, Folder 216.7)
    Article announcing the naming of Marlan Valdez as the assistant Dean for students and administrative
  - Newsletter, March 1986, 03/1986 (Box 12, Folder 216.8)
    Minutes of the meeting of the LAA board
  - Newsletter, March 1986, 03/1986 (Box 12, Folder 216.9)
    Article on the Founder's Day banquet
  - Newsletter, March 1986, 03/1986 (Box 12, Folder 216.1)
    Article honoring Judge Louis D. Harrington
  - Newsletter, March 1986, 03/1986 (Box 12, Folder 216.11)
    Article honoring two GW alumnae
  - Newsletter, March 1986, 03/1986 (Box 12, Folder 216.12)
    Series of captions for LAA photos
  - Newsletter, March 1986, 03/1986 (Box 12, Folder 216.13)
  - Newsletter, March 1986, 03/1986 (Box 12, Folder 216.14)
    Article naming Trudi Morrison as U.S. Senate Deputy Sergeant at Arms
  - Newsletter, March 1986, 03/1986 (Box 12, Folder 216.15)
    Article annoucing the death of the first president of the GWU Sun Coast Chapter
  - Newsletter, March 1986, 03/1986 (Box 12, Folder 216.16)
    Schedule of upcoming LAA events
  - Newsletter, March 1986, 03/1986 (Box 12, Folder 216.17)
    Articles for the LAA newsletter
  - Newsletter, March 1986, 03/1986 (Box 12, Folder 216.18)
    Lists of awards and achievments of GW alumni
  - Newsletter, March 1986, 03/1986 (Box 12, Folder 216.19)
    Article announcing the appointment of Lieutenant Colonel James A. Endicott as director of Law Alumni relations
  - Newsletter, March 1986, 03/1986 (Box 12, Folder 216.2)
    Article looking back upon the career of Prof.David Lowther
  - Newsletter, March 1986, 03/1986 (Box 12, Folder 216.21)
    Article which announced the awards and achievments of Stephen I. Danzansky
  - Newsletter, Sept. 1985, 09/1985 (Box 12, Folder 217.1)
    Series of articles from the GWU law center
  - Newsletter, Sept. 1985, 09/1985 (Box 12, Folder 217.2)
    Photos of members of the GWU LAA
  - Newsletter, Sept. 1985, 09/1985 (Box 12, Folder 217.3)
    Articles from the GWU LAA newsletter
  - Newsletter, Sept. 1985, 09/1985 (Box 12, Folder 217.4)
  - Newsletter, Sept. 1985, 09/1985 (Box 12, Folder 217.5)
    Letter from Teresa Crawford to Jane concerning corrections for the GWU LAA newsletter
  - Newsletter, Sept. 1985, 09/1985 (Box 12, Folder 217.6)
    Letter Ellen to Elizabeth concerning the layout of the GWU LAA newsletter
  - Newsletter, Sept. 1985, 09/1985 (Box 12, Folder 217.7)
    Articles for GWU LAA newsletter- Founders Day, Banquet Honors Jacob A. Stein and Patricia Robert Harris
  - Newsletter, Sept. 1985, 09/1985 (Box 12, Folder 217.8)
    Article for the GWU LAA newsletter announcing the appointment of James A. Endicott as the director of law alumni relations
  - Newsletter, Sept. 1985, 09/1985 (Box 12, Folder 217.9)
    Article for the GWU LAA newsletter announcing the selection of Ronald A. Willoner as the president of the GWU LAA
  - Newsletter, Sept. 1985, 09/1985 (Box 12, Folder 217.1)
    Article for the GWU LAA newsletter describing the success of the ABA reception
  - Newsletter, Sept. 1985, 09/1985 (Box 12, Folder 217.11)
    Article describing the enlargement of the National Law Center faculty
  - Newsletter, Sept. 1985, 09/1985 (Box 12, Folder 217.12)
    Previous article continued
  - Newsletter, Sept. 1985, 09/1985 (Box 12, Folder 217.13)
    Article depicting the addition of Teresa Crawfordto the Law Alumni office
  - Newsletter, Sept. 1985, 09/1985 (Box 12, Folder 217.14)
    Copy of the "President's Message"
  - Newsletter, Sept. 1985, 09/1985 (Box 12, Folder 217.15)
    Article describing the gala affair which honored the formation of a new chapter of the GWU LAA
  - Newsletter, Sept. 1985, 09/1985 (Box 12, Folder 217.16)
    Article descibing the reception which honored Maryland's Judge L. Leonard Ruben
  - Newsletter, Sept. 1985, 09/1985 (Box 12, Folder 217.17)
    Article descibing the reunion of the class of 1935
  - Newsletter, Sept. 1985, 09/1985 (Box 12, Folder 217.18)
    Article describing GWLA reception of the Florida Bar Association which honored Cliff Dougherty, retiring Law Alumni Director
  - Newsletter, Sept. 1985, 09/1985 (Box 12, Folder 217.19)
    Article describing the presentation of the Van Vleck Moot Court award to James R. Sims and Lee Epstein
  - Newsletter, Sept. 1985, 09/1985 (Box 12, Folder 217.2)
    List of GWLA events from Sept. 12 - Nov. 16
  - Newsletter, Sept. 1985, 09/1985 (Box 12, Folder 217.21)
    Caption for a photo of Stockton and Baron Hallstaken from the eighth floor of Adams Hall
  - Newsletter, Sept. 1985, 09/1985 (Box 12, Folder 217.22)
    Articles for the GWLA newsletter
  - Newsletter, Sept. 1985, 09/1985 (Box 12, Folder 217.23)
    Copy of a reservation form for the Founders Day Banquet
  - Newsletter, Sept. 1985, 09/1985 (Box 12, Folder 217.24)
  - Newsletter, Sept. 1985, 09/1985 (Box 12, Folder 217.25)
    A list of articles congratulating GWU alumni
  - Newsletter, Sept. 1985, 09/1985 (Box 12, Folder 217.26)
    A group of letters, resumes, and articles from the GWLA collections
  - Newsletter, March 1985, Reference Materials, 03/1985 (Box 12, Folder 218.1)
    Copy of the GWLA president's report
  - Newsletter, March 1985, Reference Materials, 03/1985 (Box 12, Folder 218.2)
    List of GWLA events from April 15- June 15
  - Newsletter, March 1985, Reference Materials, 03/1985 (Box 12, Folder 218.3)
    List of articles honoring GWU alumni
  - Newsletter, March 1985, Reference Materials, 03/1985 (Box 12, Folder 218.4)
    List of Obits of GWU Law Alumni
  - Newsletter, March 1985, Reference Materials, 03/1985 (Box 12, Folder 218.5)
    Article for the International Law Directory
  - Newsletter, March 1985, Reference Materials, 03/1985 (Box 12, Folder 218.6)
    Article and photo of Michelle Nardozzi honoringher reception of the Chevron Scholarship award
  - Newsletter, March 1985, Reference Materials, 03/1985 (Box 12, Folder 218.7)
    Article describing the dedication of the Jacob Burns Law library
  - Newsletter, March 1985, Reference Materials, 03/1985 (Box 12, Folder 218.8)
    Article describing the dedication of the Joseph B. Danzansky Amphitheatre class room
  - Newsletter, March 1985, Reference Materials, 03/1985 (Box 12, Folder 218.9)
    Article describing the editors of the staff of the National Law Center
  - Newsletter, March 1985, Reference Materials, 03/1985 (Box 12, Folder 218.1)
    Article announcing the retirement of the Clifford A. Dougherty
  - Newsletter, March 1985, Reference Materials, 03/1985 (Box 12, Folder 218.11)
    Article describing the suprises which ocurred at the GWU LAA luncheon
  - Newsletter, March 1985, Reference Materials, 03/1985 (Box 12, Folder 218.12)
    Article describing the festivities for the LAA onFounder's Day
  - Newsletter, March 1985, Reference Materials, 03/1985 (Box 12, Folder 218.13)
    Photo of Judge Bruce S. Mencher giving a speech to the first tear law students
  - Newsletter, March 1985, Reference Materials, 03/1985 (Box 12, Folder 218.14)
    Photo of Joseph D. Bulman recieving the GWULA Professional Achievment award
  - Newsletter, March 1985, Reference Materials, 03/1985 (Box 12, Folder 218.15)
    Two photos: the first-Martens, Crutchfield and Smegal, the second- one, untitled photo of a manphoto
  - Newsletter, March 1985, Reference Materials, 03/1985 (Box 12, Folder 218.16)
    Photo of three buildings-Lerner, Stockton and Jacob Burns Library
  - Newsletter, March 1985, Reference Materials, 03/1985 (Box 12, Folder 218.17)
    Two photos: the first-Cliff Dougherty, Don Mooer, Judge Donald Campbell and Judge Donald Carpenter; the second-Major General Lukeman and Colonel Rufus C. Young
  - Newsletter, March 1985, Reference Materials, 03/1985 (Box 12, Folder 218.18)
    Article describing the meeting of the board of directors of the LAA
  - Newsletter, March 1985, Reference Materials, 03/1985 (Box 12, Folder 218.19)
    Obituaries of members of the LAA. (Quantity-75)
  - Newsletter, March 1985, Reference Materials, 03/1985 (Box 12, Folder 218.2)
    Annual report of theImport/Export Bank of the U.S.
  - Newsletter, March 1985, Reference Materials, 03/1985 (Box 12, Folder 218.21)
    Series of Congratulations for GWU alumni
  - Newsletter, March 1985, Reference Materials, 03/1985 (Box 12, Folder 218.22)
    Letter naming Seth D. Rosen as the director of representation for the ALPA
  - Newsletter, March 1985, Reference Materials, 03/1985 (Box 12, Folder 218.23)
    Letter from Cliff to Ross regarding their latest report
  - Newsletter, March 1985, Reference Materials, 03/1985 (Box 12, Folder 218.24)
    Letter from Jerome A. Barron to Ross S. Delston regarding the 1983 annual report
  - Newsletter, March 1985, Reference Materials, 03/1985 (Box 12, Folder 218.25)
    Letter announcing the naming of Robert G. Hall an associate of Kilpatrick and Cody
  - Newsletter, March 1985, Reference Materials, 03/1985 (Box 12, Folder 218.26)
    Letter announcing the appointment of Philip Schwartz to the International Bar Assocation
  - Newsletter, March 1985, Reference Materials, 03/1985 (Box 12, Folder 218.27)
    Letter from Milton Wolson to the GWU Law school concerning the GWU Law Association Bulletin
  - Newsletter, March 1985, Reference Materials, 03/1985 (Box 12, Folder 218.28)
    Article announcing the appointment of Brigadier General Richard J. Bednar as Director of the Governemnt Contracts program
  - Newsletter, March 1985, Reference Materials, 03/1985 (Box 12, Folder 218.29)
    Article describing the Founder's Day Celebration (1984)
  - Newsletter, March 1985, Reference Materials, 03/1985 (Box 12, Folder 218.3)
    Article honoring Colonel Rufus Calhoun Young Jr.
  - Newsletter, March 1985, Reference Materials, 03/1985 (Box 12, Folder 218.31)
    Copy of the November 12, 1984 issue of the GWU report
  - Newsletter, March 1985, Reference Materials, 03/1985 (Box 12, Folder 218.32)
    Letter to Clifford A. Dougherty from Jerome A. Barron Michelle Nardozzi-the Chevron Scholarship recipient
  - Newsletter, March 1985, Reference Materials, 03/1985 (Box 12, Folder 218.33)
    Photos for the March 1985 GWU LAA newsletter
  - Newsletter, March 1985, Reference Materials, 03/1985 (Box 12, Folder 218.34)
    Letter from Jerome A. Barron to Clifford A. Dougherty
  - Newsletter, Aug. 1984, Reference Materials, undated (Box 12, Folder 219.1)
    Series of announcements of congratulations for members of the GWU LAA
  - Newsletter, Aug. 1984, Reference Materials, 12/01/1983 (Box 12, Folder 219.2)
    Announcement of new members of the law firm Crowell and Moring
  - Newsletter, Aug. 1984, Reference Materials, 03/21/1985 (Box 12, Folder 219.3)
    Copy of the March 21, 1985 president's report
  - Newsletter, Aug. 1984, Reference Materials, 08/1984 (Box 12, Folder 219.4)
    Article announcing additions to the National Law Center
  - Newsletter, Aug. 1984, Reference Materials, 08/1948 (Box 12, Folder 219.5)
    Founders Day, 1984
  - Newsletter, Aug. 1984, Reference Materials, 08/1984 (Box 12, Folder 219.6)
    Articles describing Michelle Nardozzi's reception of the Chevron Scholarship and a list a upcoming GWU LAA events
  - Newsletter, Aug. 1984, Reference Materials, 08/1984 (Box 12, Folder 219.7)
    GWU Bookstore advertisement
  - Newsletter, Aug. 1984, Reference Materials, 08/1984 (Box 12, Folder 219.8)
    Information card for the International Law center
  - Newsletter, Aug. 1984, Reference Materials, 08/1984 (Box 12, Folder 219.9)
    Article describing the semi-annual meeting of the Board of Directors of the National Law Center
  - Newsletter, Aug. 1984, Reference Materials, 08/1984 (Box 12, Folder 219.1)
    Series of Congratulatory messages for the alumni of the National Law Center
  - Newsletter, Aug. 1984, Reference Materials, 08/1984 (Box 12, Folder 219.11)
  - Newsletter, Aug. 1984, Reference Materials, 08/1984 (Box 12, Folder 219.12)
    Article announcing the retirement of Cliff Dougherty as the director of law alumni relations
  - Newsletter, Aug. 1984, Reference Materials, 08/1984 (Box 12, Folder 219.13)
    Warren Earl at the dedication of the NLC's Amphitheater classroom
  - Newsletter, Aug. 1984, Reference Materials, 08/1984 (Box 12, Folder 219.14)
    Article describing the dedication of the Danzansk
  - Newsletter, Aug. 1984, Reference Materials, 08/1984 (Box 12, Folder 219.15)
    Article describing the NY bar assoc. luncheon
  - Newsletter, Aug. 1984, Reference Materials, 05/21/1984 (Box 12, Folder 219.16)
    GW Report
  - Newsletter, Aug. 1984, Reference Materials, 08/1984 (Box 12, Folder 219.17)
    Photo copy of pictuture of a court room owned by the Law Alumni Association
  - Newsletter, Aug. 1984, Reference Materials, 07/09/1984 (Box 12, Folder 219.18)
    Letter from Bill Bennett to Mr. Dougherty and several press releases concerning the Howrey Autobiography
  - Newsletter, Aug. 1984, Reference Materials, 09/16/1983 (Box 12, Folder 219.19)
    A letter fromt Dianne F. Beemer Esquire to Clifford A. Dougherty and two articles from the local newspaper
  - Newsletter, Aug. 1984, Reference Materials, 12/15/1983 (Box 12, Folder 219.2)
    Letter from Chester C. Greer to Dean Barron concerning a recent 5x7 glossy, black and white photo
  - Newsletter, Aug. 1984, Reference Materials, 07/25/1983 (Box 12, Folder 219.21)
    Article announcing the election of John A. Hoglund as the president of the Washington State Trial Lawyer's Association
  - Newsletter, Aug. 1984, Reference Materials, 09/23/1983 --10/10/1983 (Box 12, Folder 219.22)
    Correspondences between Cliff Dougherty and other members of the LAA Series and articles
  - Newsletter, Aug. 1984, Reference Materials, 10/14/1983 (Box 12, Folder 219.23)
    Letters and articles concerning lawyer Kenneth J. Rose
  - Newsletter, Aug. 1984, Reference Materials, 03/26/1984 (Box 12, Folder 219.24)
    Copy of the Monday, March 26 1984 Daily Washington Law Reporter
  - Newsletter, Aug. 1984, Reference Materials, 05/29/1984 (Box 12, Folder 219.25)
    Letter from Marion Edwyn Harrison to Clifford A. Dougherty concerning the restructuring
  - Newsletter, Aug. 1984, Reference Materials, 01/06/1984 --01/19/1984 (Box 12, Folder 219.26)
    Letter from Edwyn Harrison to Clifford Dougherty concerning an article for alumni publication
  - Newsletter, Aug. 1984, Reference Materials, 08/1984 (Box 12, Folder 219.27)
    Advertisement for books on Patent Law fundamentals
  - Newsletter, Aug. 1984, Reference Materials, 12/12/1983 (Box 12, Folder 219.28)
    Letter and press release concerning the retirement of BG John Debarr
  - Newsletter, Aug. 1984, Reference Materials, 05/24/1984 (Box 12, Folder 219.29)
    Minutes of the GWU LAA meeting May 24 1984
  - Board of Directors, 1978-1984 (Box 13, Folder 220)
    Folder numbered Box 13, #1
  - Information sheets, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 221)
    Folder numbered Box 13, #2
  - Newsletter, 08/1984 (Box 13, Folder 222)
    Folder numbered Box 13, #3
  - Newsletter, 09/1984 (Box 13, Folder 223)
    Folder numbered Box 13, #4
  - Newsletter: 1 of 2, 09/1987 (Box 13, Folder 224)
    Folder numbered Box 13, #5
  - Newsletter: 2 of 2, 09/1987 (Box 13, Folder 225)
    Folder numbered Box 13, #6
  - Newsletter, 06/1988 (Box 13, Folder 226)
    Folder numbered Box 13, #7
  - Background Information, 09/1988 (Box 13, Folder 227)
    Folder numbered Box 13, #8
  - Jan. 1988 Newsletter, 01/1988 (Box 14, Folder 228)
    Folder numbered Box 14, #1
  - March 1987 Newsletter, 03/1987 (Box 14, Folder 229)
    Folder numbered Box 14, #2
  - March 1987 Newsletter, gallery, 03/1987 (Box 14, Folder 230)
    Folder numbered Box 14, #3
  - Sept. 1986 Newsletter, background information, 09/1986 (Box 14, Folder 231)
    Folder numbered Box 14 #4
  - Buildings and campus scenes, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 232.1)
    Includes images of Stockton Hall and Red Lion Row construction
  - Discarded slides from Building and Preservation Fund, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 232.2)
    Includes plans, models and photos of campus buildings such as the NLC, Academic Center, and Gelman Library
  - Building and construction scenes, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 232.3)
    Includes images of 2000 Penn. Ave construction
  - Buildings and classroom scenes, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 232.4)
    Includes images of Academic Center and campus yard
  - Buildings and classroom scenes, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 232.5)
    Includes images of the Burns Clinic
  - Buildings and campus scenes, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 232.6)
    Includes images of Medical School (Ross Hall, Duncan Pavilion)
- Law School printed material, RG0014 Series 14; 1.00 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains material printed for and published by the Law School.
  - Citing responsibly - a guide to avoiding plagiarism, 2000-2012; RG0014 Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Academic integrity code, 2001-2009; RG0014 Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 2-4)
  - Guide to student rights and responsibilities, 2001-2009; RG0014 Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Entering class, 1999-2008; RG0014 Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 6-7)
  - Academic awards ceremony, 2015-2016; RG0014 Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - GW Law: 150 Years of Making History, 2015; RG0014 Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 9)